Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 78, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan: Hourly and Salaried Employees, 1972; Publication (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Box: 78, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan: Hourly and Salaried Employees: UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Box: 78, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Medical Expense Program: Management and Executive Retirees, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Box: 78, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Group Accident Insurance Program: Executive, Supervisory and Administrative Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Box: 78, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Thrift-Stock Ownership Program, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Box: 78, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program: Hourly Employees: U.A.W., 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Box: 78, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program: Salaried Employees: Clerical-Engineering-Technical, 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Box: 78, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Your Insurance Program: Hourly Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Box: 78, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Your Insurance Plan: General Salaried Employees, Except Those in Collective Bargaining Units, 1962; Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Box: 78, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program - Salaried Employees: Clerical-Engineering-Technical: U.A.W., 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Box: 78, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program: Hourly Employees: U.A.W., 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Box: 78, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program: Salaried Employees: Clerical-Engineering-Technical: U.A.W., 1972; Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Box: 78, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Compensation and Benefits for Management Personnel, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Box: 78, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Compensation and Benefits: Salaried Employees: Clerical-Engineering-Technical, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Box: 78, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan: Salaried and Hourly Employees: UAW, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Box: 78, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Compensation and Benefits: Executive, Supervisory and Administrative Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Box: 78, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program: Salaried Employees: Clerical-Engineering-Technical, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 24)
- Box: 78, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan: Hourly and Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 25)
- Box: 78, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program: Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Box: 78, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Your Guide to the Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Box: 78, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan: Salaried Clerical-Engineering-Technical and Hourly Employees, 1972; Publication (Box 78, Folder 28)
- Box: 78, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan: Salaried and Hourly Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Box: 78, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Thrift-Stock Ownership Program, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Box: 78, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Your Chrysler Retirement Program: Retirement Provisions for Salaried Employees, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 31)
- Box: 78, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan: Hourly and Salaried Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Box: 78, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program: Salaried Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 33)
- Box: 78, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan: Hourly and Salaried Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 34)
- Box: 78, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program: Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 78, Folder 35)
- Box: 78, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1955; Publication (Box 78, Folder 36)
- Box: 78, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Chrysler Corporation and You: Some Things Employees Will Want to Know, 1955; Publication (Box 78, Folder 37)
- Box: 78, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Managing the Supervisor's Job, 1952; Publication (Box 78, Folder 38)
- Box: 78, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Thrift-Stock Ownership Program, Publication (Box 78, Folder 39)
- Box: 78, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Compensation and Benefits for Management Personnel of Chrysler Corporation, 1960; Publication (Box 78, Folder 40)
    Author: John D. Leary
- Box: 78, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The View from Detroit, 1955; Publication (Box 78, Folder 41)
    Author: L.L. Colbert
- Box: 78, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: What You Want to Know About Your Pension Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 42)
- Box: 78, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: What You Want to Know About Your Pension Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 43)
- Box: 78, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Moving Ahead With Chrysler: A Handbook for General Salaried Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 44)
- Box: 78, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Your Chrysler Retirement Program, 1960; Publication (Box 78, Folder 45)
- Box: 78, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Personnel Interviewing, 1953; Publication (Box 78, Folder 46)
- Box: 78, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Management Personnel Portfolio, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - Item 2: Your Guide to Management Employee Benefits, 1957; Publication (Box 78, Folder 47)
    Author: Robert W. Conder
  - Item 3: Your Guide to Salaried Employee Benefits, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 47)
- Box: 78, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 78, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Highlights of Your Pension Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 78, Folder 48)
- Box: 78, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 78, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Your Compensation as a General Salaried Employee, 1960; Publication (Box 78, Folder 49)
- Box: 78, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 50)
    Author: Gregory S. DeVine
- Box: 78, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 78, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The Group Life Insurance Plan of The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, 1968; Publication (Box 78, Folder 51)
- Box: 78, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 78, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Group Medical Insurance Plan: Covering Active and Retired Employees and Their Dependents, 1972; Publication (Box 78, Folder 52)
- Box: 78, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 78, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Group Medical Insurance Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 78, Folder 53)
- Box: 78, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 78, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Social Securityand You Under New 1950 Law, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 54)
- Box: 78, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 78, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Modified First Aid Manual, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 55)
- Box: 78, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 78, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules for Contractors and Their Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 56)
- Box: 78, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 78, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules for Office Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 57)
- Box: 78, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 78, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Employees Safety Handbook, 1962; Publication (Box 78, Folder 58)
    Author: H.M. Hart
- Box: 78, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 78, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Co-operative Wage Study Manual for Job Description Classification and Wage Administration, 1962; Publication (Box 78, Folder 59)
- Box: 78, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 78, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Co-operative Wage Study Manual for Job Description Classification and Wage Administration, 1962; Publication (Box 78, Folder 60)
- Box: 78, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 78, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pension Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 61)
- Box: 78, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 78, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Group Medical Insurance Plan, 1975; Publication (Box 78, Folder 62)
- Box: 78, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 78, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Personnel Performance Appraisal Manual: Official and Supervisory Grades, 1955; Publication (Box 78, Folder 63)
- Box: 78, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 78, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railroads Job Evaluation Manual, 1955; Publication (Box 78, Folder 64)
- Box: 78, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 78, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Introducing Canadian National, Publication (Box 78, Folder 65)
- Box: 78, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 78, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Staff Training Course, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 66)
- Box: 78, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 78, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Personnel & Labour Relations Department, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 67)
- Box: 78, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 78, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: A Study of Labour Mobility, Personnel and Labour Relations Department, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 68)
- Box: 78, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 78, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Rules: Union - Management Co-operative Movement, Equipment Department, 1963; Publication (Box 78, Folder 69)
- Box: 78, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 78, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Manual, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 70)
- Box: 78, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 78, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Management Development: Work Study Appreciation Course, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 71)
- Box: 78, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 78, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Here's Our Record in 1950, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 72)
- Box: 78, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 78, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Team Work on the Railways, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 73)
- Box: 78, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 78, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: In the Eye...in the Ear...in the Head, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 74)
    Author: Alex R. Hasley
- Box: 78, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 78, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: CN Pushes a Huge Training Program, 1966; Publication (Box 78, Folder 75)
- Box: 78, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 78, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Technological Changes in the Railway Industry, Maritime Area of CNR, 1965; Publication (Box 78, Folder 76)
- Box: 78, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 78, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Canadian National Railways Organizational Chart, 1976; Publication (Box 78, Folder 77)
- Box: 78, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 78, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Introduction to Management: Department of Industrial Education, 1955; Publication (Box 78, Folder 78)
- Box: 78, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 78, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Explanatory Statement Regarding Overtime for Supervisory Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 78, Folder 79)
- Box: 78, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 78, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Internal Revenue Service, Publication (Box 78, Folder 80)
- Box: 78, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 78, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Corporation Policy on Employee Safety, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 81)
- Box: 78, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 78, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Policy and Procedure for the Nomination, Selection, and Appointment of Management Personnel, 1958; Publication (Box 78, Folder 82)
- Box: 78, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 78, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Statement by Robert W. Conder and Norman Matthews, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 83)
    Author: Robert W. Conder; Norman Matthews
    Notes: December 11, 1950
- Box: 78, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 78, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Corporation's Statement on the Strike Settlement, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 84)
- Box: 78, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 78, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Announcement of Benefits, 1951; Publication (Box 78, Folder 85)
- Box: 78, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 78, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Chrysler has Offered Employees More Than the U.A.W. Says is 10 Cents Elsewhere, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 86)
    Notes: April 16, 1950
- Box: 78, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 78, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Makes New Offer to End 8 1/2 Week Strike, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 87)
    Notes: March 25, 1950
- Box: 78, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 78, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Etna Life Insurance Company, 1954; Publication (Box 78, Folder 88)
- Box: 78, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 78, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Chrysler's Real Pension-Insurance Benefits Backed by Company's Good Faith and Credit Rejected by UAW for 10c "Kitty" Fund, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 89)
- Box: 78, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 78, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 90)
    Author: Herman L. Wreckler
- Box: 78, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 78, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Chrysler's Offer to its Employees is Reasonable and Sound, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 91)
- Box: 78, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 78, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Chrysler Corporation's Statement on the Strike Settlement, 1950; Publication (Box 78, Folder 92)
- Box: 79, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Motors Continuing Effort to Improve the Environment, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Box: 79, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: For Your Protection, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Author: Louis C. Lundstrom
- Box: 79, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Some Facts About the GM Employee Alcoholism Recovery Program: A Brief Explanation for All Employes and Their Families, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Box: 79, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart: General Motors Corporation, 1973; Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Organization Chart: General Motors Corporation, 1973; Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Fringe Benefit Considerations in Future Bargaining, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
    Author: George B. Morris, Jr.
    Notes: January 11, 1972
- Box: 79, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Fringe Benefit Considerations in Future Bargaining, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Progress Toward Pollution-Free Cars, 1976; Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Box: 79, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Progress Toward Pollution-Free Cars, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Facts for the Guidance Counselor Advising Students on Careers in the Retail Automotive Business, 1973; Publication (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Box: 79, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of the 64th General Motors Stockholders Meeting, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Box: 79, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Press Conference Before Economic Club Speech at Cobo Hall, 1973; Publication (Box 79, Folder 8)
    Author: Richard C. Gerstenberg
    Notes: March 19, 1973
- Box: 79, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: G.M. Not Expecting Major Strike Next Year, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 7, 1972
- Box: 79, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Selling to GM, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Box: 79, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Optional Group Life Insurance Provided Under the General Motors Insurance Program for Salaried Employes, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Box: 79, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Your General Motors Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Program, 1973; Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Box: 79, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: "Help Wanted Now!": Cooperative Vocational Education, A Productive Source of New Mechanics, 1973; Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Box: 79, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Improved General Motors Insurance Program for Employes with Monthly Base Salaries of $750 or More, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Box: 79, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Your General Motors Retirement Program for Salaried Employes in the United States, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Box: 79, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Automobile Industry: A Case Study of Competition: A Statement by General Motors Corporation, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Box: 79, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Your GM Retirement Program for Salaried Employes in the United States, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Box: 79, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Your GM Savings-Stock Purchase Program for Salaried Employes in the United States, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Box: 79, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Educational Assistance for GM Salaried Employes, 1968; Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Box: 79, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: GM Mark of Excellence: Personal Accident Insurance Designed for General Motors Salaried Employees and Their Eligible Dependents, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Box: 79, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: General Motors Corporation Progress in Areas of Public Concern: GM Providing Ground, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
    Author: Edward N. Cole; James M. Roche; Richard C. Gerstenberg
- Box: 79, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Mighty Mixture, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
    Author: John F. Gordon
  - Item 2: Eighteenth Kentucky World Trade Conference, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
    Author: George Russell
    Notes: November 14, 1967
  - Item 3: Highlights: General Motors News Conference, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
    Author: Anthony De Lorenzo
- Box: 79, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Your GM Savings-Stock Purchase Program for Salaried Employes in the United States, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 23)
- Box: 79, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Strikes and Lockouts, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 24)
    Author: Louis G. Seaton
- Box: 79, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: General Motors Information Handbook, 1963; Publication (Box 79, Folder 25)
- Box: 79, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The General Motors Training Center Story, 1970; Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
- Box: 79, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: What You Should Know About Your Benefits, 1971; Publication (Box 79, Folder 27)
- Box: 79, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1960; Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
- Box: 79, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Review and Outlook, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)
    Notes: Wall Street Journal September 30, 1964
- Box: 79, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Outline of General Motors Retirement Program for Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 30)
- Box: 79, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Review of Medical Evidence of Total and Permanent Disability, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 31)
- Box: 79, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Notice of Appeal to GM-UAW Board of Administration, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 32)
- Box: 79, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Gerenal Motors Corporation Survey, 1956; Publication (Box 79, Folder 33)
- Box: 79, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Toward Your Retirement, 1960; Publication (Box 79, Folder 34)
- Box: 79, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The General Motors Insurance Program for Salaried Employes with Monthly Base Salaries of $750 or More, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 35)
- Box: 79, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Your Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Program, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 36)
- Box: 79, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Engineering Education on the Cooperative Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 37)
- Box: 79, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The College Graduate and General Motors, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 38)
- Box: 79, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: American Transit Association, 1972; Publication (Box 79, Folder 39)
    Author: R.L. Terrell
    Notes: September 27, 1972
- Box: 79, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Outline of General Motors Retirement Program for Salaried Employes, 1962; Publication (Box 79, Folder 40)
- Box: 79, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Your GM Retirement Program, 1962; Publication (Box 79, Folder 41)
- Box: 79, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: General Motors Information Handbook: A Ready Reference for Press, Radio & TV, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 42)
- Box: 79, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Right Behind the Wheel: Articles on Safe Driving From American Youth Magazine, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 43)
- Box: 79, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Your GM Savings - Stock Purchase Program for Salaried Employes in the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 79, Folder 44)
- Box: 79, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Handbook for Stenographers, 1952; Publication (Box 79, Folder 45)
- Box: 79, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The Organization of General Motors, 1953; Publication (Box 79, Folder 46)
- Box: 79, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Everyone Can Suggest: General Motors Central Office, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 47)
- Box: 79, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Management of Personnel Quarterly, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 48)
- Box: 79, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Personal Accident Insurance for General Motors Salaried Employes and Their Eligible Dependents, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 49)
- Box: 79, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Your Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Program for General Motors Salaried Employes and Their Families, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 50)
- Box: 79, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Working with General Motors, 1967; Publication (Box 79, Folder 51)
- Box: 79, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology 1939-1963, 1964; Publication (Box 79, Folder 52)
    Author: W. Willard Wirtz
- Box: 79, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology: General Motors Corp. 1939-60, 1961; Publication (Box 79, Folder 53)
    Author: Arthur J. Goldberg
- Box: 79, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 79, Folder 54)